[
  {
    "front": "envoyer, accompagner",
    "back": "送"
  },
  {
    "front": "couper, finir, tout, approcher, soigneusement",
    "back": "切"
  },
  {
    "front": "gare, station",
    "back": "駅"
  },
  {
    "front": "mer, océan",
    "back": "海"
  },
  {
    "front": "thé",
    "back": "茶"
  },
  {
    "front": "matière, matériaux, tarif",
    "back": "料"
  },
  {
    "front": "raison",
    "back": "理"
  },
  {
    "front": "rouge, pure, tout, rien",
    "back": "赤"
  },
  {
    "front": "bleu, jeune",
    "back": "青"
  },
  {
    "front": "noire",
    "back": "黒"
  }
]
